etoropartners.com 2015-05-12

# eToro Social Trading Privacy Policy | eToro

This privacy policy explains the manner in which we collect and maintain non public information about our customers (such as your full name, mailing address, identification number, passports, driver's license etc, hence forth "Information").  
**By providing us with Information, you are giving us your consent to collect, use and store the Information in the manner explained hereto.**

## When do we collect information from you?

We collect information from you when you (a) open an account and provide us with Information through electronic registration forms; (b) make a transaction with us including when you deposit and withdraw funds; Additionally, from time to time, we may collect Information about you from third party entities such as information about your credit history agencies. The Information we collect directly from you includes Information required to communicate with you such as your address, phone number, e-mail. Furthermore, we may collect other identifiable Information such as identification numbers and/or Passport/Tax registration numbers. We may also collect demographic information when you open an account, including your gender, birth date, etc. We may also need to evaluate your trading experience, average annual income, estimated net worth and make an assessment about your risk factor.

## How do we collect Information?

You directly provide us with most of the Information we collect. You do this by filling out the electronic form that we post on our website and by voluntarily providing us with other required documents. Additionally, you provide us with Information by trading on our system, by contacting us or responding to a promotion. The information we indirectly collect may include logging your Internet Protocol (IP) address, software configuration, operating system and use of Cookies; Cookies are small files sent from us to your computer and sometimes back. Cookies ultimately help us improve your navigation and ease of use of our website. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information.

## How do we use the Information collected?

### Use of Information

We use personal information only as appropriate to provide you quality service and security. For example, we may use the Information collected from you to verify your identity. We may also use this Information to establish and set up your trading account, issue an account number, issue a password, log your activity and contact you from time to time. The Information helps us improve our services to you, customize your browsing experience and inform you about additional products, services or promotions that may be of interest to you. Should you ever deactivate your account with us, we will keep your information on file, but only use it to comply with regulatory requirements and to contact you occasionally with the option to reactivate your account. Please note that you may opt out of our Information sharing policies at any time by notifying us of your desire to do so as explained below;

### Sharing Information

We do not disclose or share Information about any of our users (whether active or inactive) to any affiliated third parties or non-affiliated third parties other than in the manner and entities set forth below:

  * To service providers for the purpose of opening, operating and servicing your account. Such service providers may include attorneys, accountants, auditors, financial and other professionals;

  * To respond to a subpoena or court order, judicial process or to regulatory authorities; and

  * To protect against fraud, unauthorized transactions (such as money laundering), claims or other liabilities.

  * We do not share credit information, such as credit history, net worth, or other income information.

  * eToro OpenBook

The eToro OpenBook is a real-time social trading platform, which integrates rich community and social characteristics into the trading platform. As part of the eToro traders’ network, traders who choose to be part of the community share their strategies and performance with the community. The personal information of the traders and the amount traded is never disclosed and all traders are required to agree to be part of the network and share their strategies and performance.

If you are an existing “real account” trader by July 6, 2010 and after sending you several notification emails, we consider you as giving your permission to be part of the OpenBook community and set you as "opt-in" to the eToro OpenBook and we consider you as giving consent to this privacy policy and as accepting "passive sharing" of your trading activity (if you responded negatively to our emails you will not set as “opt-in”).

If you are a new trader, who started trading with us in a “real account” after July 6, 2010, being part of the OpenBook community is an outcome of you actively opting-in.

Whether you are a trader by or after July 6, 2010, you can always opt-in and out the OpenBook community, very simply, at your discretion.

The information that is shown on the eToro OpenBook is as following: username, full name (can be changed in the privacy settings), country, eToro Club type (gold, silver etc.), ranking, trading activity (open / close position, creating an order, earning profit), challenges activity (climbed to the Xth Position), social/community activities (following other user(s), writing comments, like / dislike), statistics [gain in % (but never amounts), winning rate in %, risk levels (low/medium/high) and instruments traded).

Click [here](https://openbook.etoro.com/settings/ "OpenBook privacy settings") to change your privacy settings.

## Third Party Data Collection

When you use or connect to eToro website or download eToro mobile app by or through a Third Party Platform, such as Facebook or other social networking site, you allow us to access and/or collect certain information from your Third Party Platform profile/account (such as your Facebook account) or via any cookies placed on your device by such Third Party Platform as permitted by the terms of the agreement and your privacy settings with the Third Party Platform. We will share such information with the Third Party Platform for their use as permitted by the terms of the agreement and your privacy setting with the Third Party Platform.”

“We will share some of the information we collect from you upon install of the mobile app with vendors and other service providers who are engaged by or working with us in connection with the operation of the services we provide to you and/or for analytics purposes which may require the reproduction and display of such information in an aggregated and anonymized manner such that will not in any way identify you.

### Third Party Data Collection - Actions

You may "opt out" of the collection of your information for third party analytics purposes by following the directions provided by our third party analytics vendor located at <http://www.mobileapptracking.com/privacy-policy/>. If you “opt out” with our third party analytics provider, that action is specific to the information we collect specifically for that provider, and does not limit our ability to collect information from you, under the terms of this privacy policy, for other vendors.

### Security and Integrity of Information

We protect your Information by using data security technology and using tools such as firewalls and data encryption. We also require that you use a personal username and password every time you access your account online. We restrict access to Information at our offices so that only officers and/or employees who need to know the Information have access to it.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to amend, revise, modify, and/or change this Privacy Policy at any time. Should we decide to make any changes to this Privacy Policy we will notify you of any such change by either posting notice on our website for public view or alternatively by notifying you by email of any changes to our policies.

### Links

Our website may contain links to other websites on the internet. We are not responsible for the content of these sites or for any other privacy practices on these internet sites. You should read the terms of use and the privacy statements of any web site that you may link to from our website that collects any information over the web. Our terms of use and our privacy policy apply only to information collected by us in accordance to this Policy.

### Updating Your Information

In the event that you believe our Information is in anyway inaccurate, please let us know immediately. We will make sure we investigate the matter and correct any inaccuracies as quickly as possible where necessary.

## Questions

Should you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at <https://www.etoro.com/application/help/contact.aspx>. Please include your name, mailing address, email and telephone number.
